Transcript and translation
from DisneyHebrewSub http://youtu.be/uIclgtW6Pfk
Thanks also Herp McDerp for posting the transcript in the comments.
Sung by מונה מור (Mona Mor)
The snow glows white on the mountain tonight,
השלג בוהק הרי הכפור
Hasheleg bohek al harei hakfor
The snow glows on the frost mountains
not a footprint to be seen
המקום ריק מלבדי
Hamakom reik milvadi
The place is empty except for me
A kingdom of isolation,
ממלכת, בדידות סוערת,
Mamlechet bdidut so'eret,
Stormy kingdom of isolation,
and it looks like I'm the queen
המלכה זו אני
hamalka zo ani
the queen is me
The wind is howling like this swirling storm inside
סוערת רוח כמו סופות ברגשותיי
So'eret ruach kmo sufot berigshotai
The wind is raging like storms in my feelings
Couldn't keep it in, heaven knows I tried
והיא רוצה לצאת ולשלוט עלי
Vehi rotsa latset velishlot alai
And it wants to get out and control me
Don't let them in, don't let them see
סוד להחביא, אל תחשפי
Sod lehachbi, lo tachsefi
Secret to hide, you won't reveal
Be the good girl you always had to be
ותהיי טובה ומלכותית
Vetihi'i tova umalchutit
And be good and majestic
Conceal, don't feel, don't let them know
כן זה סופי, לא יגלו
Ken ze sofi, lo yegalu
Yes this is final, they won't find out
Well, now they know!
טוב, עכשיו ידעו
Tov, achshav yed'u!
Well, now they'll know!
Let it go, let it go!
לעזוב, לעזוב
La'azov, la'azov!
Leave, leave!
Can't hold it back any more!
והחופש בי מתחיל לנשוב
Vehachofesh bi matchil linshov
And the freedom starts to blow inside of me
Let it go, let it go!
לשחרר, לעזוב
Leshachrer, la'azov!
Release, leave!
Turn away and slam the door!
וללכת עד הסוף
Velalechet ad hasof
And go until the end
I don't care what they're going to say
לשחרר, אין סודות יותר
Leshachrer, ein sodot yoter
Release, no more secrets
Let the storm rage on
שהסופה תסער
Shehasufa tis'ar
Let the storm rage on
The cold never bothered me anyway.
הקור לא מפריע לי לא חודר
Hakor lo mafri'a li, lo choder.
The cold doesn't bother me, doesn't invade.
It's funny how some distance
מצחיק איך לא דמיינתי
Matschik eich lo dimyanti
It's funny that I didn't imagine
Makes everything seem small
מרחק מקטין הכל
Merchak maktin hakol
That distance makes everything small
And the fears that once controlled me
הפחדים כולם שלטו בי
Hapchadim kulam shaltu bi
All of the fears that controlled me
Can't get to me at all!
זה שייך כבר לאתמול
Ze shayach kvar la'etmol!
Belong to yesterday!
It's time to see what I can do
עכשיו אוכל אולי לראות
Achshav uchal ulai lir'ot
Now maybe I could see
To test the limits and break through
מה מסוגלת לעשות
Ma mesugelet la'asot
What I'm capable of
No right, no wrong, no rules for me
אין טוב, אין רע, סוף סוף אני
Ein tov, ein ra, sof sof ani
No good, no bad, I'm finally...
I'm free!
חופשית
chofshit!
free!
Let it go, let it go!
לעזוב, לעזוב
La'azov, la'azov!
Leave, leave!
I am one with the wind and sky
לשחרר את סודות חיי
Leshachrer et sodot chayai
Release the secrets of my life
Let it go, let it go!
לעזוב, לעזוב
La'azov, la'azov!
Leave, leave!
You'll never see me cry
לא אבכה יותר ודי
Lo evke yoter vedai
I won't cry any more, that's enough
Here I stand, and here I'll stay,
כאן אני, וזה כוחי
Kan ani, veze kochi
Here I am, and this is my power
Let the storm rage on...
שהסופה תסער
Shehasufa tis'ar...
Let the storm rage on...
My power flurries through the air and to the ground
כוחי חודר מהאוויר לאדמה
Kochi choder meha'avir la'adama
My power penetrates from the air into the ground
My soul is spiralling in frozen fractals all around
נפשי רוקמת קישוטים פרועים כאן בשממה
Nafshi rokemet kishutim pru'im kan bashmama
My soul is embroidering wild decorations here in the wasteland
And one thought crystallizes like an icy blast
ומחשבה אחת צלולה מכל השאר
Umachshava achat tslula mikol hash'ar
And one thought is clearer than the others
I'm never going back
הפרק ההוא נגמר,
Haparek hahu nigmar
That chapter ended
The past is in the past!
מה שעבר עבר
ma she'avar avar!
what passed has passed!
Let it go, let it go!
לעזוב, לעזוב
La'azov, la'azov!
Leave, leave!
And I'll rise like the break of dawn
ומפה אי אפשר ליפול
Umipo i efshar lipol
And from here there is no falling
Let it go, let it go!
לעזוב, לעזוב
La'azov, la'azov!
Leave, leave!
That perfect girl is gone
לראות, לנשום, לגדול
Lir'ot, linshom, ligdol
See, breathe, grow!
Here I stand in the light of day
לשחרר, די להסתתר
Leshachrer, dai lehistater
Release, enough with the hiding
Let the storm rage on!
שהסופה תסער
Shehasufa tis'ar!
Let the storm rage on!
The cold never bothered me anyway.
הקור לא מפריע לי, לא חודר
Hakor lo mafri'a li, lo choder.
The cold doesn't bother me, doesn't invade.